Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- M
  - Moore, D. M. (class of 1846)
  - Moore, D. Thomas
  - Moore, Helen Jean (oversize) *
  - Moore, John
  - Moore, Margaret
  - Moore, Marti *
  - Moore, Mary
  - Moore, Omar Khayyam
  - Moore, Patrick S.
  - Moore, Paul A.
  - Moore, Robert
  - Moore, Robert A. *
  - Moore, Robert Y.
  - Moore, Wesley E. *
  - Moore, William E. *
  - Moorhead, J. K. *
  - Moorison, Ralph
  - Moosa, Hans H. *
  - Moosy, John
  - Moossy, John J. *
  - Mooth, Adelma E. (Dr.)
  - Morasca, Jenna
  - Morawska, Ewa
  - Moreland, Morey S.
  - Moreland, Richard L.
  - Moreno, Jose A.
  - Mores, Sherry
  - Morgan, Bill
  - Morgan, A. S. M. (Colonel) *
  - Morgan, Gilbert
  - Morgan, Lacil W. (oversize) *
  - Morgan, Marc
  - Morgan, William Alfred
  - Moriarty, Richard
  - Morinaga, Yasuko (Dr.)
  - Moriole, Deborah
  - Morley, Auleene (SEE Jamison, Auleene)
  - Mormer, Elaine
  - Morner, Magnus
  - Morrell, William *
  - Morrill, Michael
  - Morris, Allison
  - Morris, Buddy
  - Morris, Donna
  - Morris, John (Dr.)
  - Morris, Eileen J.
  - Morris, Elaine (Dr.)
  - Morris, Gregory A.
  - Morris, Nickeia
  - Morris, Robert D.
  - Morris, Robert M.
  - Morris, Toree
  - Morris, Trisha
  - Morrisey, Leslie
  - Morrisey, William D.
  - Morrison, John A. *
  - Morrow, Duane
  - Morrow, John T.
  - Morrow, Lisa
  - Morsi, Badie L.
  - Mortimer, Julie
  - Morton, Dave
  - Moses, Campbell, Jr. (Dr.)
  - Moses, Gary A.
  - Mosesso, Vince
  - Moskowitz, Merle *
  - Moson, Anna
  - Moss, Bernard
  - Moss, Carol
  - Moss, M. Gayle
  - Mosse, Daniel
  - Mossman, Mike
  - Mostoller, George A.
  - Mothupi, Carol
  - Motoyama, Etsuro K. *
  - Mott, Graham
  - Moulton, Barbara M.
  - Mountain, James *
  - Moushey, Bill
  - Mowery, Barbara
  - Mowrey, Rebecca
  - Mowry, Peter *
  - Mowry, R. B. *
  - Moye, Alfred L.
  - Moyer, Alexander
  - Mravintz, Theresa
  - Mudd, Charles Lee, Jr.
  - Mueller, Dennis
  - Mueller, Matt
  - Mufti, Aamir
  - Muhammad, Idris
  - Muir, Kenneth *
  - Mulcahy, Francis M.
  - Muldoon, Matthew
  - Mulgrave, Norman W.
  - Mulkearn, Lois (Mrs.) *
  - Mullen, Harryette
  - Mullen, Jamie A.
  - Mullennix, John W.
  - Muller, Edward K.
  - Mullin, Raya
  - Mullins, June Bonner
  - Mulry, June Grant *
  - Mulvey, Laurie
  - Mulvihill, Carol J.
  - Mulvihill, John J.
  - Mumford, John
  - Munce, Robert J.
  - Mundell, Robert D. *
  - Mundorf, Edgar A.
  - Munger, Hamnett P.
  - Munin, Michael C.
  - Munn, Norman L.
  - Munson, Patrick *
  - Munyofu, Paul
  - Murabito, Stephen J.
  - Murali, Srinivas
  - Muralt, Alexander Von *
  - Murase, Noriko
  - Murdoch, James Bissett *
  - Murdock, George P. *
  - Murphy, Albert J.
  - Murphy, Geraldine A.
  - Murphy, Ian
  - Murphy, John
  - Murphy, Robert W., Jr.
  - Murphy, Sally
  - Murphy, Sean
  - Murphy, Terry
  - Murphy, Tom (Mayor)
  - Murphy, Thomas
  - Murphy, Troy
  - Murray, John *
  - Murray, Marian
  - Murray, Sandra
  - Murrell, Audrey (Dr.)
  - Murtha, John
  - Murti, Kamakshi
  - Musahl, Volker
  - Musgrave, Ross H.
  - Muskat, Joseph
  - Musulin, R. R.
  - Myers, Cary
  - Myers, Earle
  - Myers, Ella P. (SEE Stewart, Ella P.)
  - Myers, Eugene N. *
  - Myers, Jack (Dr.) *
  - Myers, Joseph
  - Myers, Kelly
  - Myers, Mildred S.
  - Myers, Patricia A.
  - Myers, Walter L.
  - Myslinski, Casimir
- N
  - Nacy, Carol A.
  - Nader, Ralph
  - Nadler, Jacob
  - Hagata, Takesi
  - Nagle, John M.
  - Nagy, Daniel *
  - Nahmias, Rick
  - Nakada, Daisuke
  - Naples, Donna
  - Napper, Matthew A.
  - Nardini, Art
  - Narick, Emil *
  - Nash, Dorothy K.
  - Nash, Graham
  - Naski, William Z.
  - Natali, Dina
  - Nath, Raghu (Dr.) *
  - Nathonson, Esther M.
  - Nativio, Donna
  - Naunchik, Joe (oversize)
  - Naus, Gregory J.
  - Naylor, Peregin
  - Neal, Harold
  - Neal, William A.
  - Nealon, Rita Carey
  - Nebes, Robert
  - Nebolsine, Arcadi
  - Neches, William H., MD
  - Neckerman, Kathryn
  - Needleman, Herbert L.
  - Needy, Kim La Sola
  - Neese, Jim
  - Neff, Judson *
  - Negrych, James
  - Nehamas, Alexander
  - Nehnevajsa, Jiri
  - Neidle, Marks
  - Neitz, John *
  - Nelkin, Robert
  - Nelson, Glenn M.
  - Nelson, Joel
  - Nelson, Lisa
  - Nelson, Marilyn
  - Nelson, Rick
  - Nelson, Robert P.
  - Nelson, Scott
  - Nelson, W. L.
  - Nelson, William *
  - Nemento, Edwin *
  - Nemetz, Donald E.
  - Nemtsanov, Dennis
  - Nesbitt, Elizabeth
  - Ness, Roberta
  - Nessett, Kirk
  - Nesta, Frances Statti
  - Neta, Ruth
  - Netting, Craig C.
  - Netting, M. Graham (oversize) *
  - Nettleship, Ian
  - Neubauer, John (Dr.)
  - Neufield, R. D.
  - Neumer, Carol
  - Neville, Morgan
  - Nevin, Ethelbert W. *
  - Nevin, Robert Peebles *
  - Nevyas, Jacob
  - Newbury, Constance L.
  - Newby, Jerry B.
  - Newcomb, James C. (Mrs.) *
  - Newcomb, Robert *
  - Newcombe, Richard
  - Newcombe, Robert A.
  - Newell, Barbara W. *
  - Newell, David
  - Newlin, William R.
  - Newman, Anne
  - Newman, Beverly
  - Newman, Ezra
  - Newman, Jeffrey
  - Newman, Joseph
  - Newman, Michael
  - Newman, Robert P.
  - Newman, Sally
  - Newstetter, Wilbur I. *
  - Nguyen, Doan
  - Nicely, Robert F.
  - Nicholas, George A.
  - Nicholas, J. S.
  - Nichols, Bervard *
  - Nichols, Lawrence
  - Nichols, Mark
  - Nicholson, Milton E.
  - Nicklas, John
  - Nickels, Jen
  - Nicodemus, Diane
  - Nicoletti, Guy M.
  - Nicol, Louis
  - Nicoll, Allardyce *
  - Nicoletti, Guy
  - Nicotero, Greg
  - Nietz, John A. (oversize) *
  - Nilsson, Birgit *
  - Nimgaonkar, Vishwajit
  - Nissanka, H. S. S.
  - Nitko, Anthony J.
  - Nixon, Bill
  - Niyibizi, Christopher
  - Nketia, J. H. Kwabana
  - Nkunzimana, Alphonse
  - Nnaji, Bartholomew
  - Noble, Bruce
  - Noble, Harry
  - Nokali, Mahmoud El
  - Nolan, Janne E.
  - Nollan, Valerie
  - Nolle, Joyce
  - Nordan, Lewis "Buddy"
  - Norden, Carl W. (Dr.)
  - Nordenberg, Mark
  - Nordenfalk, Carl A. *
  - Norman, Liane
  - Norman, Mary (Dr.)
  - Noroian, Edward H.
  - Noroian, Elizabeth *
  - Norris, Carrie
  - Norris, Karen
  - Norris, Kimberly
  - Norris, William E.
  - North, Oliver
  - Norton, John
  - Norvell, James L. *
  - Nossen, Robert J. *
  - Notari, Charles
  - Nouchi, Sachie
  - Nous, Albert P.
  - Novacky, George A., Jr.
  - Novak, Albert J., Jr.
  - Novak, Barbara *
  - Novak, Jacqueline
  - Novak, Joseph
  - Novak, Sharon
  - Novey, John
  - Novey, Maria
  - Noviello, Susan Mather
  - Novotny, Jeff
  - Nucci, Charles (Dr.)
  - Nunes, Maria
  - Nutt, John M. *
  - Nutting, Charles B. *
  - Nwokoro, Ngozi
  - Nwosu, Sylvanus
  - Nyden, Paul *
  - Nydes, Florence
  - Nystrom, J. Warren
  - Nyswaner, Ron
- O
  - Oaks, Jeffrey
  - O'Bannon, George
  - Obermair, Gubtav
  - Obermesser, Clovis F.
  - Obern, A. Gaylord
  - Obernauer, Harold
  - Obi, Dorothy
  - Oboing, Ann B.
  - O'Brian, Barbara
  - O'Brian, Jen
  - O'Brien, Jim
  - O'Brien, Thomas
  - O'Brien-Bliel, Nancy
  - O'Brien-Schaefer, Josephine
  - Obrosky, Robert *
  - Ochester, Ed
  - O'Connell, C. Leonard *
  - O'Connell, Peta J.
  - O'Connor, Anne
  - O'Connor, Diandra
  - O'Connor, H. R. *
  - O'Connor, John
  - O'Connor, John Dennis *
  - O'Connor, Matt
  - O'Connor, Rollanda E.
  - O'Connor, William
  - Oddis, Chester
  - Odegard, Peter H. *
  - Oden, Richard
  - Odhner, Bronwyn
  - O'Donnell, Kerry
  - O'Donnell, Robert W.
  - O'Donnell, William J.
  - Oermann, Karl C. H. *
  - O'Farrell, Cathy Ann
  - Ofodile, Nkemjika
  - Ogiri-Little, Frank
  - Ogletree, Charles J., Jr.
  - Ogundayo, 'BioDun
  - Ogunleye, Shavon
  - Ohmans, John *
  - O'Keefe, Kathleen
  - O'Keefe, Stephen J. D.
  - Okolloh, Ory
  - Olander, Herbert T. (oversize) *
  - Olbum, David *
  - Olcott, H. S.
  - Olczak, Joseph A.
  - Olfman, Shama
  - Oliver, Jason
  - Oliver, John W. (oversize) *
  - Oliver, Susan
  - Oliver, Thomas *
  - Olkzak, Denise
  - Olofson, Tome
  - O'Loughlin, Johanna
  - Olsavsky, Jerry *
  - Olshansky, Ellen
  - Olson, Carl (oversize) *
  - Olson, Josephine
  - Olson, Lester C.
  - Olson, Marian
  - Olson, Richard K.
  - Olson, Robert E.
  - Oltmanns, Valerie
  - O'Malley, Bert W.
  - O'Malley, Eileen L.
  - Omanovic, Aleksandro
  - O'Mara, Jeremiah A.
  - O'Mara, Maureen
  - O'Nan, Stewart
  - Onate, Sergio
  - Onda, Ken
  - Ondaatje, Michael
  - O'Neill, Francis H.
  - O'Neill, Paul
  - O'Neill, William
  - Onn, Shao Pii
  - Ontell, Marcia *
  - Orange, Walter J.
  - Orangis, Patricia
  - Orbach, Alexander
  - Orchard, Trevor
  - O'Reilly, Anthony J. F.
  - Orenstein, David
  - Oresick, Peter
  - Orgel, Arthur *
  - Orlander, Herbert T.
  - Orlandini, Tony
  - Orlowicz, Frank
  - Ormiston, Ken
  - Ormsby-Gore, Sir William David *
  - Ornstein, Dave *
  - Orosz, Michael L.
  - O'Rourke, James V.
  - Orr, Leighton E.
  - Orr, Louis
  - Orr, Malcolm (Dr.)
  - Orr, Marquis
  - Orr, Richard *
  - Osborn, Andrew D. *
  - Osborne, Homer A.
  - Oseroff, Abraham
  - O'Shannon, Helen
  - O'Shea, Richard P. *
  - Oshry, Dee Jay
  - Oskoui, M.
  - Ostriker, Alicia Suskin
  - Oslavsky, Jerry
  - Otey, Wendell
  - Otter, Kelly
  - Otterbein, Leo
  - Ottervik, Eric V.
  - O'Toole, James M.
  - O'Toole, Kevin
  - O'Toole, Ryan
  - O'Toole, Timothy T.
  - Ottmans, Valerie
  - Ove, Peter, PhD
  - Owen, George
  - Owen, Raymond
  - Owem, Sion
  - Owens, Brian
  - Owens, Gregory R.
  - Owens, Jane
  - Owens, Samuel T., Jr.
  - Oyler, Elizabeth
- P
  - Pack, Robert Frederick
  - Packer, Z. Z.
  - Paddon-Row, Michael
  - Padunov, Vladimir
  - Page, Gregory
  - Page, Julius
  - Page, Lorne A.
  - Page, Mary
  - Pager, John
  - Pagliano, Fiore
  - Pagliaro, Claudia
  - Pagonis, Irene
  - Paige, Kenneth *
  - Painter, Michael
  - Pak, Heinz
  - Palascak, Edward S.
  - Palascak, Margaret
  - Palchak, Joseph F.
  - Palko, Tyler
  - Palmer, Anthony Ray
  - Palmer, Catherine V.
  - Palmer, Laura
  - Palmer, Trudy
  - Palmiere, Eric J.
  - Palmieri, Paolo
  - Palumbo, Nicole
  - Pamphilis, Stephen
  - Panah, Assad
  - Pandolph, Eugene
  - Panetta, W. C.
  - Panvity, L. S.
  - Paolino, Dariana
  - Paolone, Vittorio
  - Papale, Vic
  - Pape, Robert
  - Pappas, George (Dr.)
  - Paradise, Jack
  - Paransky, Leah
  - Pardini, Brenda J.
  - Parham, James
  - Parikh, Urvi
  - Paris, Melissa
  - Paris, Paul
  - Park, Graham
  - Park, Jean
  - Park, Richard L. *
  - Park, Uhnsook
  - Parkas, Iva
  - Parker, Alexander *
  - Parker, Joseph J.
  - Parker, Robert S.
  - Parker, Theodore Roosevelt
  - Parker, Thomas
  - Parkham-Vetter, Christy
  - Parkinson, David
  - Parmanto, Bambang
  - Parniak, Michael A.
  - Parran, Thomas *
  - Parrendo, Nick
  - Parrett, Arthur N.
  - Parslow, Robert
  - Parsons, Keith M.
  - Parsons, Lois *
  - Partanen, Carl R. (Dr.)
  - Pascusio, Anne *
  - Pasek, Tracy Ann
  - Pasqualichio, Joseph
  - Pasquerilla, Frank J.
  - Paquerilla, Mark E.
  - Patusiak, Longin
  - Patel, Amit
  - Patel, Rita *
  - Patla, Wanda
  - Patno, Mary Ellen
  - Patouillet, Leland
  - Patrick, Thelma E.
  - Patry, Matthew
  - Pattak, Evan
  - Patterson, Charles D.
  - Patterson, Ellen J. *
  - Patterson, Gary T.
  - Patterson, Louise *
  - Patterson, Orlando
  - Patterson, Robert *
  - Patterson-Randles, Sandra R.
  - Patterson, Thomas H. B. *
  - Patterson, Thomas W.
  - Pattison, F. W.
  - Patton, Robert A. *
  - Paul, Barbara
  - Paul, Greg
  - Paul, John W.
  - Pauly, Thomas
  - Paulin, Dorothy C. *
  - Pauina, Judy
  - Paulston, Christina
  - Paulston, Rolland G.
  - Paulus, John D.
  - Pavia, John W.
  - Payne, C. R.
  - Payne, Dan
  - Payton, Nicholas
  - Pazin, George
  - Peake, Charles H. *
  - Peart, Tasha
  - Pease, N. Ronald *
  - Pechan, Albert R. *
  - Pecora, Pat
  - Pederson, Steven C.
  - Pedulla, Marisa
  - Peel, Robert L. *
  - Peele, Pamela B.
  - Peery, Rex
  - Peever, Irvin
  - Pegula, Laura
  - Pei, Mario (Dr.) *
  - Peirce, John *
  - Pekor, Renee
  - Peline, Val P.
  - Pellegrini, Fausto
  - Pelusi, Jamie
  - Pelusi, John H., Jr.
  - Peluso, Robert
  - Pemberton, Sandy
  - Penich, Jamie
  - Penny, Rob
  - Pentico, David *
  - Pentland, Abner Lacock *
  - Pentland, Andrew W. *
  - Pentland, Ephraim *
  - Pepe, Janelle
  - Pepper, George Wharton
  - Pepper, Lisa
  - Perchersky, Jack
  - Perez, Carlos
  - Perez, Louis
  - Perez-Darilla, Alfredo
  - Perez-Linan, Anibal
  - Perfetti, Charles
  - Perjean, Helen (Sister)
  - Perkins, Dexter *
  - Perkins, Douglas
  - Perkins, Kenneth
  - Perkins, Wilma Lord
  - Perland, Patrick *
  - Perle, Eugene D.
  - Perlman, Lawrence
  - Perlman, Mark *
  - Perlmutter, David H.
  - Perloff, Evelyn
  - Perloff, Robert
  - Permar, Ed
  - Permar, Howard H.
  - Permyashkin, Varia
  - Perry, Emanuel
  - Perry, Steven H.
  - Pertzman, Andrew
  - Perutz, Max
  - Peski, Mindy
  - Peskie, Angela
  - Petek, Hrvoje
  - Peterman, Harry
  - Peters, B. Guy
  - Peters, Leonard K.
  - Petersen, Gertrude
  - Petersen, James B.
  - Petersen, John M.
  - Peterson, Carl Alfred *
  - Peterson, Christian
  - Peterson, Craig
  - Peterson, Edwin L. (oversize) *
  - Peterson, Edward N.
  - Peterson, Janet
  - Peterson, Joel E.
  - Peterson, John E.
  - Peterson, Karen
  - Peterson, Vida M. *
  - Petesch, Donald
  - Petitti, Rob
  - Petprin, Andrew
  - Petor, Mary (SEE Phillips, Mary)
  - Petro, Steve L.
  - Petroff, Larry
  - Petrosky, Kristy
  - Petrosky, Tony
  - Petrovsky, Michael
  - Pettegrew, Jay
  - Pettigrew, Chenits
  - Pettit, Alma Metz
  - Pettit, Frederick S.
  - Peuloff, Robert *
  - Pfeffer, J. Alan (Dr.) *
  - Pfister, Damien
  - Pham, Si Mai
  - Pharr, Ann E.
  - Phebus, Carol K. *
  - Phelps, Harold A. *
  - Philbrick, Thomas *
  - Philippon, Marc
  - Phillippi, Grover
  - Phillips, C. J.
  - Phillips, Eugene
  - Phillips, Joseph J. (Captain)
  - Phillips, Marie Tello
  - Phillips, Francis Clifford *
  - Phillips, Mary Viola Petor *
  - Phillips, Suzanne
  - Phitayak, Preyaratt *
  - Phule, Pradeep P.
  - Picard, Louis
  - Piccicotti, Dustin
  - Pickett, Galen
  - Picker, Eke
  - Piemme, T. *
  - Pierce, Calvin J.
  - Pierce, Gordon Barry
  - Pierce, James
  - Pierce, Leslie S.
  - Pierce, Richard "William"
  - Pil, Frits K.
  - Pilant, Walter L. *
  - Pilgram, Francis J. (oversize) *
  - Pilgram, Martin W.
  - Pilkonis, Paul
  - Pincus, Harold
  - Pinder, J.
  - Pinsky, Michael R. *
  - Pinza, Claudia
  - Pierri, Joseph N.
  - Pipas, James
  - Piposzar, David
  - Piraino, Beth M.
  - Pistella, Christine L.
  - Pitcairn, Robert
  - Pitt, Bruce
  - Pitt, William *
  - Pittenger, Rex A.
  - Pittman, Keith *
  - Pivovar, Perri Lael
  - Placek, Joseph
  - Plakans, Andrejs
  - Plamenac, Dragon *
  - Plank, David
  - Plankey, Francis
  - Plant, Tony
  - Plants, Pat *
  - Plants, Patricia
  - Platt, David *
  - Platt, Thomas
  - Plazek, Don
  - Pleasant, Charles (Rev.)
  - PLotnick, Harold L.
  - Plumb, John B.
  - Pocar, Fausto
  - Pochapin, Sherman W.
  - Poe, George
  - Poel, William (oversize)
  - Pogue-Geile, Katherine
  - Pohland, Frederick G.
  - Pois, Joseph (Dr.) *
  - Poke, Carl A.
  - Poke, Carl F.
  - Polchak, Jake
  - Poling, Harold
  - Polite, Lousaka
  - Polk, Kenneth J.
  - Pollack, Allen *
  - Pollack, Ian
  - Pollack, John C. *
  - Pollack, Martha
  - Poller, Jennifer L.
  - Polletta, Francesca
  - Polley, Mary
  - Pollock, H. O.
  - Poltoratsky, Nickolai Petrovich
  - Polts, James
  - Pomeroy, Richard H. *
  - Pond, Allen
  - Ponko, Mark
  - Pontius, Robert G.
  - Poole, Bernard
  - Poole, Harry *
  - Poole, Marion L. *
  - Poole, Rachel I. J.
  - Pope, S. E.
  - Popovich, Paul S.
  - Popper, Lewis M.
  - Porat, Joan
  - Pore, Dave
  - Porsche, Robert William Anthony
  - Porsching, Thomas
  - Porter, Barbara L.
  - Porter, Chad
  - Porter, Curtiss
  - Porter, Darelle
  - Portis, Audrey
  - Portner, Irving A. *
  - Porvaznik, Drew
  - Porzecanski, Arturo C.
  - Posner, Mitchell C.
  - Post, Klaus-Dieter
  - Postell, Malcolm
  - Postlethwaite, James
  - Posvar, Mildred Miller (Mrs. Wesley W.) *
  - Posvar, Wesley W. (Dr.) (oversize)
  - Poteat, Hank
  - Potoski, Brian A.
  - Potra, Florian
  - Potter, John H.
  - Potter, Robert L.
  - Poulakos, John
  - Pounds, Lois A. *
  - Pourarian, Faiz
  - Powell, Edward
  - Powelson, John P.
  - Power, Howard A. (Dr.)
  - Powers, David R. *
  - Powers, Gerald T.
  - Powers, Philip H.
  - Powers, P. O.
  - Praity, C. E.
  - Prall, Charles E.
  - Pratapas, Mike
  - Prater, N. H.
  - Pratt, David S.
  - Pratt, David W.
  - Pratt, Elizabeth Ann
  - Pratt, Minnie Bruce
  - Pratt, Richard *
  - Pratt, Robert
  - Pratt, Sheila
  - Pray, Francis
  - Prentice, Nikkisha
  - Prescott, John
  - Pressley, John Talor (Rev.) *
  - Preston, William (Dr.) *
  - Pretto, Ernesto
  - Previn, Andre
  - Pribbernow, Michelle
  - Price, Fredric
  - Price, Gwilym A. *
  - Price, Henry
  - Price, W. Conway (Dr.) *
  - Price-Mobley, Sandra
  - Priestly, David
  - Priman, Jacob
  - Primo, Albert
  - Primus, H. Raymond (Dr.)
  - Primus, Fred
  - Prinz, Diane K.
  - Prior, Michele
  - Priselac, Thomas M.
  - Probert, Harry A.
  - Proctor, Ralph (Dr.)
  - Prokop, Paul J., Jr.
  - Pron, Mike
  - Prostrednik, Stanley
  - Pruchnic, Ryan J.
  - Prunty, Howard E.
  - Prycl, Margie
  - Pryde, Thomas
  - Przybylski, Gregory
  - Przymusinska, Halina
  - Przymusinski, Teodor
  - Ptachcinski, Richard J.
  - Pucevich, Ryan
  - Pugh, Paul M.
  - Pugliano, Fiore
  - Puglisi, Catherine
  - Puig-Antich, Joaquim *
  - Puri, Shalini
  - Purifoy, Amir
  - Purins, Girts
  - Puskar, Kathryn
- Q
  - Qian, Angi
  - Qualters, Robert
  - Quatroche, John
  - Quatse, Jess
  - Quick, John Gilbert (oversize) *
  - Quider, Anna
  - Quimby, Peter
  - Quimpo, Rafael G.
  - Quinlan, Robert M.
  - Quintana, Humberto "Bert"
  - Quintyne, Nicholas
- R
  - Rabell, Carmen
  - Rabkin, Michael S. *
  - Rabin, Bruce S.
  - Rabinowitz, Joni
  - Rackham, Jeff
  - Racunas, Robert V.
  - Radcliff, Douglass
  - Radecic, Peri Jude
  - Radford, Edward
  - Rafferty, Denise C.
  - Rafferty, Thomas F.
  - Ragan, William A.
  - Raghavan, Kalyani
  - Ragni, Margaret V.
  - Ragsdale, Ronald G.
  - Rahaman, Azizur
  - Raines, William P.
  - Rajasekaran, Baskaran
  - Rajagopal, Kumbakonam
  - Rall, Esther H.
  - Rall, Trish
  - Ralph, Charles L. *
  - Ramage, Rich
  - Ramalingam, Sakkaraiappan
  - Ramanathan, Ramesh
  - Ramey, Irene
  - Ramicone, Arthur
  - Ramirez, John
  - Ramon, Ronald
  - Ramos, Teofilo J.
  - Ramp, Robert
  - Ramsey, Lorraine E.
  - Ramsey, Michael
  - Ranaganathan, Shiyale Ramamrita
  - Ranalli, Dennis
  - Ranciere, Jacques
  - Rancurello, Michael
  - Randolph, Norman
  - Rango, William
  - Rankin, Alan Carson *
  - Rao, B. Raja
  - Rao, C. R.
  - Rao, R. Harsha
  - Rao, Kanchan H.
  - Rao, Marepalli
  - Rapone, Nick
  - Rapp, Robert *
  - Rappeport, J. J.
  - Rasch, C. H.
  - Raschen, John
  - Ratcliff, James R.
  - Rasmussen, Edie *
  - Rathbone, Donald E.
  - Rathbun, Daniel Boardman
  - Rathgeber, Lewis R.
  - Rathke, Sheila
  - Rattay, Fran
  - Ravenstahl, Luke
  - Ravitch, Mark M.
  - Rawlings, Jerry John
  - Rawski, Evelyn S.
  - Rawski, Thomas
  - Rawson, Christopher
  - Ray, Charles Kingsley *
  - Ray, Lieutenant C.
  - Ray, Charlotte *
  - Ray, Julius
  - Ray, Oakley S. *
  - Ray, William S. *
  - Raybuck, Janice
  - Rayman, Jamie
  - Raymond, James
  - Rea, Brad
  - Rea, Ingrid Shellabarger
  - Rea, William H. *
  - Reacher, Nicholas
  - Reading, Reid
  - Reagle, Barbara W.
  - Reardon, Lawrence C.
  - Reavis, George H.
  - Rebek, Julius Jr.
  - Recker, Perry *
  - Reddy, Nirmala *
  - Reddy, Ravinder
  - Reddy, Sudhakar
  - Redfern, Mark
  - Redfield, Charles E. *
  - Rediker, Marcus
  - Redinbaugh, Ellen
  - Redmond, Carol
  - Reed, Carl (and Ida)
  - Reed, Chad
  - Reed, David Aiken
  - Reed, Frank
  - Reed, James Calvin
  - Reed, James Hay
  - Reed, Joel
  - Reed, John
  - Reed, Lowell
  - Reed, Pearl
  - Reed, Ralph
  - Reed, Sykes
  - Rees, Carl
  - Reeves, Ann
  - Regan, William J.
  - Regueiro, Miguel D.
  - Rehm, Jane *
  - Rehm, Lynn
  - Reich, Harvey *
  - Reich, Simon
  - Reichlin, Seth
  - Reichner, Philip
  - Reid, Leon *
  - Reid, Marlene
  - Reid-Brossard, Paki
  - Reif, Edward C.
  - Reiker, Richard
  - Reilly, James *
  - Reinbold, Ronald G.
  - Reinecke, Gustav *
  - Reineman, Adam *
  - Reinhart, John B. (Dr.)
  - Reinhart, Todd
  - Reinmuth, Oscar
  - Reiser, Oliver L. (oversize)
  - Reis, Steven
  - Reisner, Gerald S.
  - Reisser, Catherine E. (Dr.)
  - Reist, Katherine K.
  - Reiter, Burkhardt
  - Reitell, Charles
  - Reizner, Burton R.
  - Relyea, Rick
  - Remler, R. F.
  - Rendell, Edward G.
  - Renick, Stacy
  - Renk, William T.
  - Renland, Patrick R. (Dr.)
  - Rentler, Oxanna Kaufman (SEE Kaufmann, Oxanna)
  - Renton, Arthur D.
  - Repasi, Barbara
  - Replogle, Gretchen (Mrs. Arnold M.) *
  - Replogle, John
  - Rescher, Nicholas *
  - Resnick, Lauren
  - Resnick, Neil
  - Resnick, Robert
  - Resnick, Sandy
  - Reuschlein, Harold Gill *
  - Reuter, Henry F.
  - Revay, Andrew W. *
  - Revis, Darrelle
  - Reynolds, Carroll *
  - Reynolds, Charles, III
  - Reynolds, Ian J.
  - Reynolds, James C.
  - Reynolds, James H.
  - Reynolds, Jean *
  - Reynolds, Jessica
  - Reza, Ali *
  - Rezek, Donald L.
  - Reznik, Jay *
  - Rheinboldt, Werner C.
  - Rhinesmith, Stephen H.
  - Rhoades, Linda
  - Rhoads, Edward
  - Rhodes, Arthur R. *
  - Rhoten, Don
  - Ribisl, Richard P. (Dr.)
  - Ribman, Ronald
  - Ribner-Smith, Doris A.
  - Ricci, Edmund
  - Rice, Doug
  - Rice, Lester
  - Rice, Martin
  - Rice, Robert V.
  - Rice, Ted
  - Rich, Demetrious
  - Rich, Olive J.
  - Richards, Shirley
  - Richardson, Archie M. (Dr.) *
  - Richardson, Eliot *
  - Richardson, Eugene C.
  - Richardson, Gale A.
  - Richardson, James
  - Richardson, James B., III
  - Richardson, Kenneth T. (Dr.) *
  - Richardson, Robert W.
  - Richey, DeWayne G.
  - Richlin, Laurie
  - Richman, Estelle B.
  - Richman, Raymond *
  - Richter, Jake
  - Rickert, John (Dr.)
  - Ricordi, Camillo *
  - Riddle, David H. *
  - Riddle, L. E.
  - Riddle, M. B.
  - Riddle, Walther
  - Riddler, Sharon A.
  - Riddenaur, William P. *
  - Ridgway, Matthew (General) *
  - Ridinger, Charles W. *
  - Ridge, Tom (Governor)
  - Ridl, Charles "Buzz"
  - Ridley, Todd J.
  - Riechenberg, Kurt
  - Riefler, Roger F.
  - Rieker, Richard Allen
  - Rifkin, Lester
  - Riley, Richard H. *
  - Rimer, J. Thomas
  - Rinaldo, Charles
  - Rinear, David L.
  - Ringer, Fritz K.
  - Rinehart, Mary Roberts
  - Ripalda, Enrique *
  - Ripley, Brian
  - Ripoll, Marla
  - Rissman, Michael
  - Rist, D. Wes
  - Ritenour, Walter M.
  - Rittenberger, Jon
  - Riva, Humbert L. *
  - Rivera-Garza, Christina
  - Ro, Kong Kyun
  - Roach, Robert
  - Roach, William A.
  - Roat, Melvin I.
  - Robb, Mary Cooper
  - Robb, Robert
  - Robbins, Paul
  - Robensteen, John E.
  - Roberson, Edward
  - Roberts, Doris J.
  - Roberts, Grady H.
  - Roberts, James M.
  - Roberts, James W.
  - Roberts, Jay (Dr.)
  - Roberts, John M.
  - Roberts, Laurel Bridges
  - Roberts, Marcie
  - Roberts, Mark S.
  - Roberts, Mary M. (Dr.)
  - Roberts, Merril J. *
  - Roberts, Roy
  - Roberts, Samuel *
  - Robertsthaw, John A., Jr.
  - Robertson, Anne
  - Robertson, Kellie
  - Robertson, Mary Ella (oversize)
  - Robertson, Robert J.
  - Robertson, William, Jr.
  - Robie, Fred S. *
  - Robin, Eugene D.
  - Robin, Gilbert N. (Dr.)
  - Robin, John P.
  - Robinson, A. C.
  - Robinson, A. L. (oversize) *
  - Robinson, Betty (SEE ALSO Robinson, Jimmy Joe)
  - Robinson, Charles J.
  - Robinson, Donald H.
  - Robinson, Eleanor M.
  - Robinson, Jimmy Joe
  - Robinson, Joanne
  - Robinson, Karen
  - Robinson, Marshall A.
  - Robinson, Paul N.
  - Robinson, Roscoe
  - Robinson, Shawn
  - Robinson, William, Jr. *
  - Robinson, William R.
  - Robitaille, Denis
  - Rocerete, La Verne (Mrs.)
  - Rock, James *
  - Rockenbach, Barbara
  - Rockman, Bert A. (Dr.)
  - Rocks, Beth
  - Rockwell, Charles J.
  - Roderick, David M.
  - Rodd, Priscilla
  - Roddey, Jim
  - Rodgers, J. Albert
  - Rodgers, James *
  - Rodin, Judith